giveawayblogs.com 2012-10-17

# Privacy Policy - Giveaway Blogs

GiveawayBlogs.com gathers information when a user registers on GiveawayBlogs.com, post information on the site, or fills out a form. A user may be asked to enter personal information not limited to name and email address. Any information collected may be used to personalize user experience, to improve the website, or to administer a contest, promotion, survey, or other feature. Information may also be used to send emails to user regarding information, responses to inquiries and requests, and to send company updates, announcements, and promotional offers from Digital Room, Inc. GiveawayBlogs and its content is public. GiveawayBlogs cannot guarantee that all content and information submitted on the site will not be copied, saved or shared.

In compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act, this privacy policy may be easily accessed from the GiveawayBlogs Homepage. Users of the Site may make any changes or updates to their information at any time by logging into their accounts and accessing their Profile Pages.

GiveawayBlogs.com requires registration and/or a password for access. Information obtained from registered users may also be used for GiveawayBlogs marketing purposes, and cookies may be used in those and other areas, as is described in this Policy. Information obtained in these areas may also be used in accordance with agreements governing access to and use of the specific areas.

A cookie is a series of data characters that, when programmed into a web site, is placed by the web server into the browser’s application folder on your computer. Once placed onto your machine, the cookie will allow the web site to “recognize” you as a unique individual. GiveawayBlogs uses Cookies to personalize information for certain segments of its customer base; and in some instances, to allow GiveawayBlogs the opportunity to associate individual customers with their information profiles. For example, through the use of cookies, GiveawayBlogs can “remember” your user ID when you login to GiveawayBlogs on your computer. GiveawayBlogs also uses cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so we may offer better user experience in the future. Should you choose to do so, cookies can be removed from your hard drive and certain web browsers can be set so that cookies are not used or saved. Please check with your browser provider for more information on removing cookies.

Our policy is to not give, sell or otherwise distribute the information collected through this site to third parties outside of Digital Room, Inc. and its subsidiaries (unless required by law); provided, however, in some cases we may use suppliers to assist us in collecting, using or otherwise processing for our benefit the information obtained through this site.

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

At the discretion of GiveawayBlogs, third party products, services, or links may be shared on the website. These third parties have privacy policies that are separate and independent of GiveawayBlogs. GiveawayBlogs therefore does not assume any responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these sites.

GiveawayBlogs allows members the option to opt-out of any marketing communications upon request. Once your information is received, you may be sent marketing communications that contain valuable offers, promotions and other content. Those who no longer wish to receive such communications may opt-out by following the directions contained in the communication. Marketing communications from GiveawayBlogs will tell you how to stop receiving them.

Contact Details:

Our postal address is: GiveawayBlogs Digital Room Inc. 8000 Haskell Avenue, Van Nuys, CA 91406

We can be reached via email at admin@giveawayblogs.com or by telephone at (888) 888-4211.

GiveawayBlogs reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time with or without notice. Please check back frequently in the event of changes.

Your use of GiveawayBlogs constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy.
